http://www.seopt.com/privacy/

Call: (713) 518-2159
e-mail: sean@seopt.com
PrivacyHomeAboutSearch Engine OptimizationLocal Houston SEOPPC CampaignsHouston SEO ConsultantSite DesignSocial MediaContactBlogResourcesLocal CitationsGood ReadsGeneral DirectoriesHome › PrivacySeOpt.com respects your privacy.Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of SeOpt.com.Credit card details
SeOpt.com will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on SeOpt.com.External Sites
SeOpt.com is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information. We may partner with 3rd party ad or content delivering services to deliver relevant ads or content to our visitors.Cookies
A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows SeOpt.com to recognize you each time you visit this site(customization etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and SeOpt.com does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.Other Information We Collect
We collect information about our visitor’s domain, but we collect no information about our visitor’s email address.For visitors on our website we collect:
Aggregate (General Tracking) information about pages that users visit on our site.The information that we collect is used for:Internal review, tracking, or contacting and is then archived for future reference.Improving the quality of our website content and user friendliness for a better user experience.Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The InternetWhile we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to SeOpt.com and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through SeOpt.com have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.
Contact Us
Your Name (required)
Your Email (required)
Phone (required)
Subject
Get In Touch SeOpt, Inc.24044 Cinco Village Center Blvd
Suite #100Katy, TX 77494 (713) 518-2159 sean@seopt.comURL of Map
NavigateHomeSearch Engine MarketingLocal Houston SEOPPC Campaign ManagementHouston SEO ConsultantSocial MediaContact UsSitemapResourcesRecommended ReadingGeneral DirectoriesLocal CitationsSite DesignAbout UsBlogPrivacyPartners
Copyright ©
2013 SeOpt.com Internet Marketing - All Rights Reserved
www.seopt.com
